sideincomeblogging.com 2019-02-28

# Disclaimer and Privacy Policy - Side Income Blogging

_**Forgive me, but I have to put on my lawyer voice for a minute:**_

### Disclaimer

Any information shared on Side Income Blogging is provided for information and entertainment purposes only and does not constitute financial advice. Side Income Blogging is intended to provide general information only and does not attempt to give you advice that relates to your specific circumstances. You are advised to discuss your specific requirements with an independent financial adviser.

In accordance with the latest FTC guidelines, we declare that we have a financial relationship with every company mentioned on this site. For product or service reviews we may have either received the product or access to the service for free. For product and service giveaways, we may have received the product or access to the service for free.

We do link out products or services using affiliate links. This means that when you purchase a product or service using one of our links, we get paid a commission. There is no additional cost to you as a result. Additionally, we only link out to products and/or services that we have personally used and endorse. Maintaining a trust relationship with our readers is critically important to us.

Any rates or third party offers listed on this site change without notice and may be out of date. For the latest rate or offer information please consult with the institution or organization. We endeavor to keep all information up to date but that’s not always possible given how quickly things change.

### Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://sideincomeblogging.com/contact/).

At Side Income Blogging, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Side Income Blogging and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, Side Income Blogging makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.sideincomeblogging.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Side Income Blogging.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Side Income Blogging and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense, Commission Junction and others.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Side Income Blogging send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Side Income Blogging has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Side Income Blogging’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

_**Ok, lawyer speak over!**_
